hey everyone and welcome back to my
channel i am so glad you're here
i'd love for you to hit that subscribe
button down below click the little bell
and turn on all post notifications if
you haven't already
and join me here on my channel today i'm
going to share a pedal and pup
spring try on haul with you guys and i
am so excited about these outfits they
are beyond cute
and they have me so ready for sunshine
and warmer weather
i think you guys are really going to
enjoy what i picked out and i do have a
discount code for you guys too so
let's go ahead and get started all right
so to start off my discount code is my
first name rachel and that'll get you 20
off petal and puffs entire website which
is so awesome you can get some really
cute new pieces
for spring and summer time and save a
little bit too with that code and i
wanted to start off with what i think is
one of my favorite things i'm going to
try on for you guys today
i am such a dress kind of girl i know
i've mentioned that before
i would choose a dress every day if i
could that's why i am so excited for
warm weather and sunshine to get here
and this dress is just beyond cute it's
feminine like i love
and the pattern and the colors are so
pretty for spring and summer time
i love it paired with a straw hat and
i'll show you guys a close-up too so you
can see the pretty details
i love the like pink and coral it's got
the little ruffle details and the floral
print
and the sleeves are really cute too
they're just kind of billowy and they've
got the ties and the drawstring tie
right here as well
and then it's got the two tone with the
ruffle on the bottom
it's just perfection i know i will live
in this dress
and it could not be any more comfortable
it's just so lightweight
easy breezy and effortless and it will
be so fun to style with all kinds of
different accessories
different straw hats pretty necklaces
some fun statement earrings
and definitely a straw bag and either
some cute sandals or
wedges or you could also do some like
white espadrilles sneakers i
love pairing sneakers with dresses and
when they have that like espadrille heel
that just adds that like spring and
summertime feel to it so
you guys have absolutely got to get this
dress for yourself
it is just beyond cute and i wanted to
show you guys too how adorable this
dress looks paired with a fun straw
clutch or a tote bag or something
and for size reference on this dress i'm
wearing the size 8 and it's perfect
i'm 5'7 for height reference and this is
the length on me
it's perfect it's not too short by any
means
i just absolutely love this little dress
next up is another darling dress and i
absolutely love
this pretty bubble gum pink color by the
time winter is over
i am just so ready for all things bright
and colorful and happy
and this dress definitely does the trick
i cannot wait to wear this when it warms
up
and i love the style of it too it's
again just very effortless
lightweight it just kind of makes you
want to twirl around in this dress
i love the two tiers to it and the
sleeves are really pretty too
just kind of billowy like that other
dress very relaxed
and the little v-neck is cute so you can
add on all kinds of fun necklaces
some statement earrings any accessories
that you want to add on would be so cute
with this dress
add a pop of color to it as well and
then i've just got this paired with some
little white espadrilles sneakers
i told you guys i love that combination
i think it looks so cute and it's
definitely one of my go-to combos for
spring and summer time
and this dress as well as the first one
that i tried on are both great for
springtime because they do have sleeves
so that way when it's still just a
little bit chilly out at times or like
if you're headed out to dinner in the
evening and you want to wear one of
these
you do have a little bit of something
covering your arms and you could always
like tie a denim jacket around your
waist so that you have that you could
add on an extra layer with this
but it is just beyond cute i know you
guys would love it as much as i do
and i'm also wearing the size 8 in this
dress that's typically the size that i
wear in petal and pups dresses
and i believe this one also comes in
other colors too i think there might
even be a white which
i love a good little white dress they're
some of my favorites and most worn so
i might have to get this dress in the
white too because i love it that much
and all of these outfits and little
dresses would be perfect if you're
headed on like a spring break vacation
or even a staycation
these would be so cute to take with you
you could add on like a big fun tote bag
or a pool bag or something like that
just definitely outfits that you will
get a lot of wear out of
next up is this darling top and i love
this pretty like sandy neutral color
it reminds me of the beach because i
desperately wish i was at the beach
right now
and this is just such a great and very
versatile top for spring and summer time
you can style this lots of different
ways you can keep it super casual just
with some cute cut off shorts and
accessories
or you could totally dress it up and
pair it with like some white denim and
then you could even add on a denim
jacket on top if you need an extra layer
if it's still kind of chilly out
you could do this with some jeans wedges
i've just got on
my espadrilles sneakers you can do
sandals whatever you want
and then just dress it up with some fun
accessories a hat
you could do a pretty headband or some
cute hair clips or something like that
and then you could also add on a pop of
color like with some colorful statement
earrings but
i thought it was just so cute and again
i love how effortless and relaxed it is
it's got the two tiers of ruffles love
those feminine details
and cute sleeves too i feel like
everything i'm trying on today has
fun sleeves on it which i love and then
here it is just with a fun little straw
crossbody bag
this would totally be like one of my
go-to outfits this is right up my alley
totally my style and i think you guys
would love this top too
and then i've got one more dress to
share with you all and i think that this
dress is so much fun for spring and
summer
i love the sleeves on it they're so cute
and the polka dot print
i love a good statement sleeve and these
are just really cute
and poofy they've got the ruffle detail
and i liked the smocked top on it too
and then it's just loose and relaxed on
bottom but i have always loved this like
pretty
mustard golden color for spring and
summer it looks even better when you
have a little bit of a tan so i cannot
wait for that but
i think it's just such a pretty color it
looks really great with gold so i always
love to add on some gold layering
necklaces
like some big gold hoops like this and i
think it looks pretty with like this
straw too
so of course my favorite accessory is
straw hat and a straw bag
and then i just added on the white
espadrille sneakers to go with the
little white polka dots
you could do some sandals wedges or like
some lace-up sandals
whatever you want to do would be so cute
with this and for size reference on this
dress i'm wearing the size large and i
will say
it's the shorter of the three dresses
that i've tried on definitely not too
short to wear by any means or i wouldn't
wear it but
i just wanted to make sure to mention
that it is a little bit shorter than the
other two so just keep that in mind and
again for height reference i
am 5'7 and then we've got one more
pretty top and you really
can never have too many great little
white tops and white dresses
they're some of my favorites to collect
so i was excited to add this pretty top
to my collection
but they're just so versatile for spring
and summer time because you can style
them with all kinds of different
accessories and make
lots of different looks whether you want
to add on some fun pops of color to the
white
or keep it simple and go for like an
all-white look or just add on some
pretty gold or silver jewelry
and i loved the style of this top kind
of like everything else i've tried on
it's just that like
loose oversized fit that i love and of
course the three tiers of ruffles the
more ruffles the better
and it's just kind of one of those swing
tops that kind of makes you want to
twirl around like that dress that i
tried on it's got the pretty sleeves
and it's just such a great top that i
know i'll get a lot of wear out of
and i added on one of my favorite blush
pink hats for a little pop of color
and then i love it with denim shorts you
can leave it untucked or you could do
like a little half tuck too
or you could even tie this in a knot
which would be really cute
and then you can totally add on some
jeans and some pretty sandals or wedges
i've just got on some little white
sandals and for size reference in this
top i've got on the size large
alright so that's it for this petal and
pop spring try on haul i hope you guys
enjoyed this video
be sure to give it a thumbs up if you
did and everything is linked right down
below in the description box as always
as well as my discount code
rachel for 20 off your entire order on
petal and pop's website
which is awesome so you can stock up and
grab some cute new pieces for spring and
summer time and save a little bit too
i hope that tryon gave you guys some fun
outfit inspiration as well and i've also
listed down below with the links
the sizing info for everything that i
was wearing just to help give you guys a
little size reference
and you'll have to comment down below
let me know what your favorite outfit
was
i love to hear from you all and thank
you so much for watching i'll talk to
you next time
[Music]
bye